http://www.simplyblooms.com/customer-service/privacy-policy/

Occasions
Special Occasions
ChristmasGet WellRosesAnniversaryJust BecauseSympathy - FuneralBirthdayLove and RomanceSympathy - HomeCongratulationsNew BabyThank YouEverydayPatriotic Arrangements
Upcoming Occasions
DEC25Christmas DayDEC31New Year's EveJAN01New Year's DayJAN18Martin Luther King Jr. DayJAN24National Compliment DayJAN26Military Spouse's Day
Christmas
Christmas Flowers
Best Sellers
Clear Vase ArrangementsColored Vase ArrangementsBasket ArrangementsCenterpiecesPlants/Dish GardensHoliday Gifts
Best Sellers
Holiday Joyful Wishes Bouquet
From
$60
Bringing Joy Basket
From
$60
Red Poinsettia
From
$60
Upcoming Occasions
DEC25Christmas DayDEC31New Year's EveJAN01New Year's DayJAN18Martin Luther King Jr. DayJAN24National Compliment DayJAN26Military Spouse's Day
Everyday
Everyday
Best Sellers
Clear Vase ArrangementsColored Vase ArrangementsBasket ArrangementsPlants/Dish GardensGift Baskets
Best Sellers
Sapphire Skies Bouquet
From
$70
Modern Elegance Bouquet
From
$60
Vibrant Garden Bouquet
From
$70
Upcoming Occasions
DEC25Christmas DayDEC31New Year's EveJAN01New Year's DayJAN18Martin Luther King Jr. DayJAN24National Compliment DayJAN26Military Spouse's Day
Birthday
Birthday Flowers
Best Sellers
Clear Vase ArrangementsColored Vase ArrangementsBasket ArrangementsPlants/Dish GardensBalloonsPackaged SpecialsGift Baskets
Best Sellers
Pretty Please Bouquet
From
$60
Supreme Birthday
From
$90
Sapphire Skies Bouquet
From
$70
Upcoming Occasions
DEC25Christmas DayDEC31New Year's EveJAN01New Year's DayJAN18Martin Luther King Jr. DayJAN24National Compliment DayJAN26Military Spouse's Day
Sympathy
Sympathy
Best Sellers
Sympathy ArrangementsSympathy PlantsSprays and WreathsFloor BasketsPatriotic ArrangementsTreasured MomentsGift BasketsFor the Home
Are you delivering to a Funeral or another location?
Sympathy - Funeral
Sympathy - Home
Anniversary
Anniversary
Best Sellers
Clear Vase ArrangementsColored Vase ArrangementsBasket ArrangementsPlants/Dish GardensRosesBalloonsPackaged SpecialsGift Baskets
Best Sellers
How Sweet It Is Bouquet
From
$65
Sapphire Skies Bouquet
From
$70
Together Forever Bouquet
From
$65
Upcoming Occasions
DEC25Christmas DayDEC31New Year's EveJAN01New Year's DayJAN18Martin Luther King Jr. DayJAN24National Compliment DayJAN26Military Spouse's Day
Flowers
Special Flowers
RosesCarnationsLiliesAlstroemeriaDaisies
Best Sellers
Roses
Daisies
Lilies
Upcoming Occasions
DEC25Christmas DayDEC31New Year's EveJAN01New Year's DayJAN18Martin Luther King Jr. DayJAN24National Compliment DayJAN26Military Spouse's Day
Plants
Plants
Green PlantsDish GardensBlooming Plants More
Best Sellers
Green Plants
Dishgardens
Blooming Plants
Upcoming Occasions
DEC25Christmas DayDEC31New Year's EveJAN01New Year's DayJAN18Martin Luther King Jr. DayJAN24National Compliment DayJAN26Military Spouse's Day
Gifts
Gifts
Sympathy FuneralSympathy HomeBirthdayGet WellAnniversaryNew BabyThank You More
Best Sellers
Crayola Creative Time Box
Delivery Included
$80
Up to Par Golfer Box
Delivery Included
$85
Birthday Party in a Box
Delivery Included
$87
Upcoming Occasions
DEC25Christmas DayDEC31New Year's EveJAN01New Year's DayJAN18Martin Luther King Jr. DayJAN24National Compliment DayJAN26Military Spouse's Day
Quick Shop
Select OccasionAnniversaryBirthdayCongratulationsGet WellJust BecauseLove & RomanceNew BabySympathy & FuneralThank You
Choose Delivery Date
Clear
Shop Now
Customer Service - Orders, Deliveries, Policies...
At Blooms Today, we are an industry leader in providing delivery services on a wide variety of flowers and gifts. Your complete satisfaction is our top priority and every order comes with our 100% Money-Back Guarantee. We strive to exceed our customer's expectations with quality, value and service.
Home
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
Resources
About Us
Our Commitment
Service
Commitment
Secure Shopping
Blooms Today makes ordering easy, convenient, and safe. Any private information submitted to us (including credit card numbers, names, addresses, and telephone numbers) is encrypted using SSL (secure socket layer) technology ensuring that private information cannot be read as it crosses the Internet. Blooms Today does not store any credit card information on our web site, so your billing information is not accessible by others.
Collection and Use of Information
• Ordering: Placing an order requires providing us with personal contact and billing information, including your name, address, email address and telephone number. This information is used to give our customers a more personalized experience and to process orders quickly and efficiently. We do not save your credit card information on our web site. A recipient's telephone number is used for delivery purposes only. There are times when we may have to contact recipients to schedule delivery or to ensure their satisfaction with our product.
• Use of Email Addresses: Blooms Today will use customer email addresses for periodic communications. For example, we may contact you about feedback on your experience with us, or provide you with promotional offers. If you no longer wish to receive these messages, please click the unsubscribe button at the bottom of the email.
• Technical Information: As customers visit BloomsToday.com, we collect some standard non-identifying information. This typically includes information regarding a visitor's operating system, browser software, and IP (Internet Protocol) address. This information is collected in order to provide the highest number of visitors with the best possible service. We may use this information to help us detect problems with our server and to administer our web site.
• Third-Party Use: Blooms Today must share certain information with our floral and gift distributors for the exclusive purpose of delivering your orders. We may make your information available to selected third parties including, but not limited to, those who share or rent information for direct marketing purposes.
• Links to Other Sites: BloomsToday.com may contain links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices and content of these third-party web sites. We strongly urge you to follow safe Internet practices; please do not supply personal information to these websites unless you have verified their security and privacy policies.
• Credit Cards: Purchasing from BloomsToday.com requires a valid credit card.
• Consent: By shopping at BloomsToday.com you consent to the use of your personal information in the manner specified by our privacy policy. We may change, modify, or add to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy at any time. These changes will be posted on the web site as appropriate and will be effective from the date of posting. Blooms Today is operated in the United States. If you are located outside the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using our web site or otherwise providing us with information, you hereby consent to this transfer. Although personal information collected by us through our web site, emails, mail, fax, and telephone is used by us in accordance with this privacy policy, laws generally applicable to the protection of personal data in the U.S. may not be as stringent as those in other countries. If you submit data to us about other individuals (such as your message and gift recipients), you agree, and we assume, that you have obtained consent from each such individual to the submission, transfer and processing of the information. If you would like to update or correct information previously provided to us, please send an e-mail with your new information, including your complete name, postal address, and email address to concerns@bloomstoday.com
How Can We Help You?
(800) 359-5309
Chat
Email
Blooms TodayAttn: Customer Service13575 Wellington Center CircleSuite 101Gainesville, VA 20155
Flower delivery is not availablefor this location.
We can ship from ourGift Basket Collection instead.
best live chat
